Guide to the Carl Van Vechten Papers Relating to African American Arts and Letters
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1932–1964; Series IV; 157.31 linear feet
  - Selected Photographic Prints, 12.51 linear feet
    - Photographic Prints
      - Portraits
        - Brown, Debria, as Carmen in Carmen, opera by Georges Bizet and libretto by Henri Meilhac and Ludovic Halévy, 1958 December 15; 10 photographic prints (Box 85, Folder 1434)
          Roll number VIII qq.
        - Brown, Gabriel, 1935 November 28; 11 photographic prints (Box 85, Folder 1435)
          Roll number XXXII i.
        - Brown, Gabriel, 1935 November 28; 8 photographic prints (Box 85, Folder 1436)
          Roll number XXXI i.
        - Brown, Marion "Spoons," in This Is the Army, musical with music by Irving Berlin and book by Irving Berlin and James McColl, 1942 August 11; 6 photographic prints (Box 85, Folder 1437)
          Roll number XIX w.
        - Brown, Scoogie, and Alfonso Marshall, 1954 September 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 85, Folder 1438)
          Roll number I mm.
        - Brown, Scoogie, and Geoffrey Holder, 1954 September 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 85, Folder 1439)
        - Brown, Scoogie, with Geoffrey Holder and Alfonso Marshall, 1954 September 2; 1 photographic print (Box 85, Folder 1440)
        - Browne, Roscoe Lee, 1964 January 14; 3 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1441)
          Roll number XIV uu.
        - Bryant, Joyce, 1953 May 28; 10 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1442)
          Roll number XVIII kk.
        - Bubbles, John W., as Sportin' Life in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1935 December 27; 16 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1443)
          Roll number XXXVI i.
        - Bubbles, John W., as Sportin' Life in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1935 December 27; 8 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1444)
          Roll number XXXV i.
        - Bunche, Ralph J. (Ralph Johnson), 1951 May 16; 13 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1445)
          Roll number X ii.
        - Burleigh, H. T. (Harry Thacker), 1941 October 23; 13 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1446)
        - Burley, Dan, 1947 November 13; 2 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1447)
          Roll number XXI dd.
        - Burton, Miriam, 1958 May 10; 5 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1448)
          Roll number XXV m.
        - Burton, Miriam, and Diedre Greenway, 1958 May 10; 2 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1449)
        - Calloway, Cab, 1933 January 12; 52 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1450-1451)
          Roll number XX b.
        - Calloway, Cab, 1933 January 12; 44 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1452-1453)
          Roll number XIX b.
        - Campbell, Dick, 1944 February 29; 3 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1454)
          Roll number XIX z.
        - Carlis, John, Jr., 1958 November 11; 1 photographic print (Box 86, Folder 1455)
          Roll number V qq.
        - Carpenter, Thelma, 1949 March 9; 11 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1456)
          Roll number XXV ff.
          Carpenter wears a Seminole costume, and a Hopi/Navajo silver squash blossom necklace.
        - Carroll, Diahann, 1955 March 14; 21 photographic prints (Box 86, Folder 1457)
          Roll number XII mm.
        - Carter, Jack, 1937 April 15; 5 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1458)
          Roll number XXIV k.
        - Carter, Jack, as Lonnie Thompson in Stevedore, play by Paul Peters and George Sklar, 1934 April 25; 6 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1459)
          Roll number XIV f.
        - Carter, Jack, as Lonnie Thompson in Stevedore, play by Paul Peters and George Sklar, 1934 April 25; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1460)
          Roll number XIII f.
        - Carter, John Wallace, 1958 November 18; 5 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1461)
          Roll number VI qq.
        - Carter, Shirley Venett, 1961 August 8; 1 photographic print (Box 87, Folder 1462)
          Roll number XIII ss.
          Also known as Shirley Verrett-Carter.
        - Cartwright, Uriah J., 1942 November 13; 7 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1463)
          Roll number XI x.
          An inscription refers to nickname "Nat."
        - Case, Bertha, and Sarah Victor, 1933 May 12; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1464)
          Roll number XXI c.
        - Cayton, Horace R. (Horace Roscoe), at Fisk University, Nashville, Tennessee, 1947 April 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1465)
        - Chookasian, Lili, 1964 May 5; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1466)
          Roll number I vv.
          Chookasian was an Armenian American.
        - Clay, Fannie S., 1933 January 25; 1 photographic print (Box 87, Folder 1467)
          Roll number I c.
        - Clay, Fannie S., and Bill Robinson, 1933 January 25; 1 photographic print (Box 87, Folder 1468)
        - Clay, Fannie S., and Bill Robinson, 1941 April 18; 4 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1469)
          Roll number XXIV t.
        - Clay, Omar, 1962 October 30; 1 photographic print (Box 87, Folder 1470)
          Roll number XI tt.
        - Cleveland, Lady Bird, 1954 September 21; 5 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1471)
          Roll number III mm.
          Also known as Lady Bird Strickland.
        - Cleveland, Lady Bird, and Patricia Cleveland, 1959 July 28; 1 photographic print (Box 87, Folder 1472)
          Roll number XVIII oo.
        - Cleveland, Lady Bird, with her painting, Eartha Kitt, 1954 October 5; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1473)
          Roll number VI mm.
        - Coan, Shirley, with Herbert Rutherford, A. D. Watson, and Jackson Wheeler, singers performing in Bar Harbor, Maine, 1936 July 25; 1 photographic print (Box 87, Folder 1474)
          Roll number XXXI j.
          Identified left to right as Rutherford, Coan, Watson, and Wheeler.
        - Cole, James, 1932 June 19; 18 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1475)
          Roll number Aa.
        - Cole, Louis, at Paris, France, 1934 June 15; 22 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1476-1477)
          Roll number XXXIV f.
        - Cole, Louis, at the Champs-Élysées, Paris, France, 1934 June 16; 10 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1478)
          Roll number XXXV f.
        - Coleman, Leo, as Toby in The Medium, opera by Gian Carlo Menotti, 1946 May 18; 13 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1479)
          Roll number I cc.
        - Collins, Durward, 1962 September 5; 6 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1480)
          Roll number IX tt.
        - Collins, Janet, in La Creole, dance choreographed by Janet Collins, 1949 April 23; 10 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1481)
          Roll number V gg.
        - Collins, Janet, in Rondo, ballet from Eine Kleine Nachtmusik, composed by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, choreographed by Janet Collins, 1949 April 23; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1482)
          Roll number VI gg.
        - Collins, Janet, in Spirituals, dance choreographed by Janet Collins, 1949 April 23; 6 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1483)
          Dancing to the spirituals, "Nobody Knows the Trouble I've Seen" and "Didn't My Land Deliver Daniel."
        - Collins, Zebedee, 1953 February 10; 5 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1484)
          Roll number VIII kk.
          Shogolo Oloba (also known as the Federal Theater African Dance Troupe) was a dance company founded by Asadata Dafora.
        - Collins, Zebedee, and Lorenzo Newby, 1953 February 10; 6 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1485)
        - Collins, Zebedee, and Lorenzo Newby, 1953 February 17; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1486)
        - Cook, Muriel, and Lawaune Kennard in Black Ritual (Obeah), ballet choreographed by Agnes de Mille, music by Darius Milhaud, 1940 April 8; 1 photographic print (Box 87, Folder 1487)
        - Cook, Muriel, with Lawaune Kennard and Dorothy Williams in Black Ritual (Obeah), ballet choreographed by Agnes de Mille, music by Darius Milhaud, 1940 April 8; 2 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1488)
        - Cooper, Maurice, 1939 April 24; 3 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1489)
          Roll number XVII o.
        - Cooper, Maurice, as Nanki-Poo in The Swing Mikado, musical by Gentry Warden, based on The Mikado; or, The Town of Titipu, a comic opera by Arthur Sullivan and libretto by W. S. Gilbert, 1939 April 24; 20 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1490)
        - Corbin, Clayton, 1954 October 23; 10 photographic prints (Box 87, Folder 1491)
          Roll number V mm.
          Three prints have inscription by Corbin to Langston Hughes; formerly formed part of the Langston Hughes bequest.
        - Cortor, Eldzier, 1959 June 7; 5 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1492)
          Roll number XXIX ii.
        - Cortor, Eldzier, with his artwork, 1959 June 7; 4 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1493)
          Artworks identified by Van Vechten as Head Study and Composition Heads.
        - Cromer, Edward, at the home of Mary A. Bell, 18 Greenwich Park, Boston, Massachusetts, 1938 July 2; 4 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1494)
          Roll number XXX m.
        - Cross, James "Stump", in This Is the Army, musical with music by Irving Berlin and book by Irving Berlin and James McColl, 1942 August 11; 3 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1495)
          Roll number XX w.
        - Cross, James "Stump," and William "Stumpy" Wyckoff in This Is the Army, musical with music by Irving Berlin and book by Irving Berlin and James McColl, 1942 August 11; 5 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1496)
        - Cullen, Countee, 1941 June 15; 4 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1497)
          Roll number XVII u.
        - Cullen, Countee, at Central Park, New York City, 1941 September 20; 13 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1498)
          Roll number XIII v.
        - Curtis, Robert, 1955 April 19; 11 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1499)
          Roll number XVI mm.
        - Dafora, Asadata, as Bridegroom and with a drummer in Kykunkor (The Witch Woman), opera by Asadata Dafora, 1935 January 17; 4 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1500)
          Roll number XXVIII g.
          Drummer is one of the cast members, either Exebro Ejiho, Uno Eno, Sakor Jar, or Abrodun Salakox.
        - Dafora, Asadata, as Bridegroom in Kykunkor (The Witch Woman), opera by Asadata Dafora, 1935 January 17; 6 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1501)
        - D'Alvarez, Marguerite, with Paul Moor and Clément Richer at Marché aux Puces de Saint-Ouen, Paris, France, 1949 October 9; 1 photographic print (Box 88, Folder 1502)
          Roll number XXV gg.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1932 March 5; 2 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1503)
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1932 June 18; 2 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1504)
          Roll number Y.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1933 June 26; 14 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1505)
          Roll number VI d.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1933 June 26; 16 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1506)
          Roll number VII d.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1934 January 9; 7 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1507)
          Roll number XXX e.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1937 July 11; 3 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1508)
          Roll number XLII k.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1938 December 21; 11 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1509)
          Roll number XXIII n.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, 1963 January 29; 2 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1510)
          Roll number XVIII tt.
          Inscription on one print misidentifies the date as February 12, 1963.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, and Kenneth Macpherson with a Head of Jimmie Daniels by Richmond Barthé, 1938 December 21; 2 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1511)
          Roll number XXIV n.
        - Daniels, Jimmie, and Tonio Selwart, 1932 March 5; 2 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1512)
        - Daniels, Jimmie, with sculpture, Head of Jimmie Daniels, by Richmond Barthé, 1938 December 21; 7 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1513)
        - Daniels, Jimmie, with sculpture, Head of Jimmie Daniels, by Richmond Barthé, 1938 December 21; 1 photographic print (Box 88, Folder 1514)
        - Davis, Jimmy, 1942 July 27; 9 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1515)
          Roll number XVI w.
          One print has an inscription by Davis to Langston Hughes, Christmas 1942; formerly formed part of the Langston Hughes bequest.
        - Davis, Jimmy, 1942 December 28; 5 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1516)
          Roll number XVII x.
        - Davis, Ossie, 1951 April 12; 2 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1517)
          Roll number VIII ii.
        - Davis, Ossie, and Ruby Dee, 1961 November 15; 2 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1518)
          Roll number XVII ss.
        - Davis, Ossie, as Gabriel in The Green Pastures, play by Marc Connelly adapted from Ol' Man Adam an' His Chillun by Roark Bradford, 1951 April 12; 8 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1519)
        - Davis, Ossie, as Gabriel, and William Marshall as God in The Green Pastures, play by Marc Connelly adapted from Ol' Man Adam an' His Chillun by Roark Bradford, 1951 April 12; 5 photographic prints (Box 88, Folder 1520)
        - Davy, Gloria, 1958 February 22; 2 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1521)
          Roll number II qq.
        - Davy, Gloria, in Aida, an opera by Giuseppe Verdi with libretto by Antonio Ghislanzoni, 1958 February 22; 9 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1522)
          Roll number I qq.
        - Davy, Gloria, in Aida, an opera by Giuseppe Verdi with libretto by Antonio Ghislanzoni, 1958 February 22; 4 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1523)
        - Dawson, William L. (William Levi), 1934 November 21; 12 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1524)
          Roll number XVI g.
        - Day, Carita, at Fisk University, Nashville, Tennessee, 1947 April 25; 1 photographic print (Box 89, Folder 1525)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, 1955 March 3; 1 photographic print (Box 89, Folder 1526)
          Roll number XI mm.
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, and Geoffrey Holder, 1955 March 3; 2 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1527)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, and Leo Holder, 1958 December 26; 5 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1528)
          Roll number X qq.
        - De Paur, Leonard, 1958 November 11; 3 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1529)
        - De Paur, Leonard, and Norma Childs De Paur, 1958 November 11; 2 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1530)
        - De Paur, Leonard, at the opening of The Art of the Negro in Dance, Music and Drama exhibition at the Museum of the City of New York, 1958 June 17; 3 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1531)
          Roll number XXXIX m.
        - Dee, Ruby, 1961 November 15; 7 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1532)
        - Dee, Ruby, 1962 September 25; 15 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1533)
          Roll number X tt.
        - Delaney, Beauford, 1953 March 18; 4 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1534)
          Roll number XII kk.
        - Delaney, Hubert Thomas "Hap", 1935 March 22; 3 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1535)
          Roll number I h.
        - Delaney, Hubert Thomas "Hap", 1935 March 22; 1 photographic print (Box 89, Folder 1536)
          Roll number XLIII g.
        - Demby, William, 1956 March 13; 3 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1537)
          Roll number XI oo.
        - Dilworth, Hubert, 1963 August 28; 4 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1538)
          Roll number X uu.
        - Dixon, Aland, 1937 July 15; 2 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1539)
        - Dixon, Dean, 1941 September 17; 19 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1540)
          Roll number XII v.
          One print has an inscription by Dixon to "Walter."
        - Dobbs, Mattiwilda, 1955 January 26; 18 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1541)
          Roll number IX mm.
        - Dodson, Owen, 1942 June 18; 15 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1542)
          Roll number VIII w.
        - Douglas, Aaron, 1933 April 10; 8 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1543)
          Roll number XV c.
        - Dove, Evelyn, 1935 December 27; 4 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1544)
        - Dove, Evelyn, 1935 December 27; 11 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1545)
          Roll number XXXVII i.
        - Dover, Cedric, 1948 February 25; 1 photographic print (Box 89, Folder 1546)
          A self-identified Eurasian with an English father and Indian mother. Dover had a long standing interest in African American art.
        - Dover, Cedric, 1948 April 15; 7 photographic prints (Box 89, Folder 1547)
          Roll number VI ee.
        - Du Bois, Shirley Graham, 1946 July 18; 3 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1548)
          Roll number VIII cc.
          Identified by Van Vechten as Shirley Graham.
        - Du Bois, W. E. B. (William Edward Burghardt), 1946 July 18; 11 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1549)
        - Dunbar, Rudolph, 1946 September 28; 12 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1550)
          Roll number XI cc.
        - Duncan, Todd, 1947 June 19; 9 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1551)
          Roll number VII dd.
        - Dunham, Katherine, 1940 May 10; 33 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1552-1553)
          Roll number XI r.
        - Dunham, Katherine, 1940 May 10; 11 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1554)
          Roll number X r.
        - Dunn, Blanche, 1934 January 9; 8 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1555)
        - Dunn, Blanche, 1941 May 10; 28 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1556-1557)
          Roll number VII u.
        - Eaton, Roy, 1958 December 2; 5 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1558)
        - Edward, Jon, in The Firebird, ballet by Igor Stravinsky and choreographed by Michel Fokine, 1938 March 25; 13 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1559)
          Roll number VI m.
        - Edward, Jon, in The Firebird, ballet by Igor Stravinsky and choreographed by Michel Fokine, 1938 March 25; 4 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1560)
        - Edwards, Mary Perkins, 1941 July 15; 3 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1561)
          Roll number XXV u.
        - Edwards, Mary Perkins, and Julius, Perkins, Jr., 1941 July 15; 3 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1562)
        - Elzy, Ruby, as Serena in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1935 December 30; 11 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1563)
          Roll number XL i.
        - Elzy, Ruby, as Serena in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1935 December 30; 11 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1564)
          Roll number XXXIX i.
        - Essen, Abdul, as Witch Doctor in Kykunkor (The Witch Woman), opera by Asadata Dafora, 1935 January 17; 3 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1565)
        - Essen, Viola, as the Courtesan, with Kari Karnakoski as the Prince, and Francisco Moncion as Sebastian in Sebastian, ballet choreographed by Edward Caton, 1944 November 20; 4 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1566)
          Roll number XIV aa.
        - Essen, Viola, as the Princess, and Francisco Moncion as Sebastian in Sebastian, ballet choreographed by Edward Caton, 1944 November 20; 5 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1567)
          Roll number XVI aa.
        - Evans, Bobby, 1942 March 19; 10 photographic prints (Box 90, Folder 1568)
          Roll number XXV v.
        - Evanti, Lilllian, 1935 October 31; 3 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1569)
          Roll number XXV i.
        - Fitzgerald, Ella, 1940 January 19; 38 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1570-1571)
          Roll number XIV q.
        - Flowers, Martha, 1953 February 17; 11 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1572)
          Roll number IX kk.
        - Garland, Bennie, Jr., and Isabelle Saunders Garland, 1939 April 23; 2 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1573)
          Affixed to one of the prints a holiday greeting from Marinoff and Van Vechten as well as a title for the image, A Harlem Madonna.
        - Gibson, Althea, 1958 November 20; 11 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1574)
          Roll number VII qq.
        - Gibson, Althea, 1958 November 20; 15 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1575)
        - Gibson, Richard, 1959 January 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1576)
          Roll number XII qq.
        - Gillespie, Dizzy, 1955 December 2; 16 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1577)
          Roll number I oo.
        - Gillespie, Dizzy, with a painting by Karl Priebe, 1955 December 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1578)
        - Goode, Eslanda, and Paul Robeson, Jr., 1945 February 15; 3 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1579)
          Roll number XXXVII g.
        - Gordon, Taylor, 1933 March 18; 9 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1580)
          Roll number X c.
        - Grant, Frances O. (Frances Olivia), 1937 July 11; 3 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1581)
        - Green, Frank, and William R. Valentine Barnes at the home of Albert C. (Albert Coombs) Barnes, Lower Merion Township, Pennsylvania, 1940 February 4; 1 photographic print (Box 91, Folder 1582)
          Roll number XVI q.
          Green and Valentine were singers in the chorus at the Manual Training and Industrial School for Youth at Bordentown, New Jersey
        - Green, Lil, 1942 March 19; 4 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1583)
        - Green, Lil, 1942 March 19; 11 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1584)
        - Grist, Reri, 1959 December 8; 11 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1585)
          Roll number VI rr.
        - Grist, Reri, 1959 December 15; 5 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1586)
          Roll number VII rr.
        - Guillén, Nicolás, 1949 March 23; 2 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1587)
          Roll number II gg.
        - Guillén, Nicolás, and Langston Hughes, 1949 March 23; 2 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1588)
        - Hall, Juanita, 1953 March 26; 1 photographic print (Box 91, Folder 1589)
          Roll number XIII kk.
        - Hall, Juanita, as Bloody Mary in South Pacific, musical composed by Richard Rodgers with lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, and book by Oscar Hammerstein II and Joshua Logan, 1949 June 25; 18 photographic prints (Box 91, Folder 1590)
          Roll number XII gg.
        - Hallaway, Mary Lee, 1939 May 16; 3 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1591)
          Roll number XXIV o.
        - Handy, Elizabeth, 1932 May 24; 2 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1592)
          Roll number S.
        - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1932 May 24; 11 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1593)
        - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1941 June 30; 6 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1594)
          Roll number XX u.
        - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1941 July 17; 8 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1595)
          Roll number I v.
        - Harvey, Georgette, 1932 May 23; 4 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1596)
          Roll number Q.
        - Hawkins, Barry, 1961 April 11; 1 photographic print (Box 92, Folder 1597)
          Roll number VI ss.
        - Hawkins, Barry, and Veronica Tyler, 1961 April 11; 2 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1598)
        - Hayes, Afrika, 1964 March 24; 2 photographic prints (Box 92, Folder 1599)
          Roll number XVIII uu.
        - Hayes, Lauren, 1964 August 18; 1 photographic print (Box 92, Folder 1600)
          Roll number VI vv.
        - Hayes, Marion, 1962 November 20; 1 photographic print (Box 92, Folder 1601)
          Roll number XIV tt.